Guide to the Tony Judt Papers MC 233
New York University Archives
- Series II: Articles/Essays
  - Subseries A: Notes, Drafts and Research
    - Review of Syndicalist Legacy: Trade Unions and Politics in Two French Cities in the Era of World War One, circa 1987 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - "A Nose for a New Idea," review of The Foul and the Fragrant: odor and the French social imagination, TLS, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Review of Rethinking the French Revolution: Marxism and the Revisionist Challenge, circa 1987 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - "Debating the Nature of Dissent in Eastern Europe," occasional paper for the Wilson Center, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - "Debating the Nature of Dissent in Eastern Europe," occasional paper for the Wilson Center, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - "The Dilemma of Dissidence," Eastern European Politics and Societies, circa 1988 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Review of Mai 68: L'Enre-Deux de la Modernite. Histoire de Trente Ans, circa 1988 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - "Moving Pictures," Radical History Review, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Review of 2 books on 20th century France for The Journal of Modern History, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Review of 2 books on Western educational systems, TLS, circa 1990 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - "A nation-builder and his successors," review of T.G. Masaryk - Volume Two: Thinker and Critic, TLS, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - "A nation-builder and his successors," review of T.G. Masaryk, Vol. 2, TLS, draft, correspondence, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - "A nation-builder and his successors," review of T.G. Masaryk, Vol. 2, TLS, research, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - "A nation-builder and his successors," review of T.G. Masaryk, Vol. 2, TLS, notes, research, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - "A nation-builder and his successors," review of T.G. Masaryk, Vol. 2, TLS, research, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Review of Syndicalism in France: A Study of Ideas, circa 1990 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - "The Unmasked Future: What Prospects from Eastern Europe?" Tikkun, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - "The Rediscovery of Central Europe," Daedalus, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Review of Disturbing the Peace: A Conversation with Karel Hvizdala, Boston Globe, draft, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - "The War Between the French," review of 7 books on Vichy France, TLS, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - "The War Between the French," review of 7 books on Vichy France, TLS, research, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - "The War Between the French," review of 7 books on Vichy France, TLS, notes, research, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - "The War Between the French," review of 7 books on Vichy France, TLS, notes, research, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Review of "La République: 1880 à nos jours," Revue, circa 1990 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - "Modern Times," review of The Birth of the Modern, FanFare, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - "The Past Echoes in the 'New' Europe," Boston Globe, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - "Justice as Theatre," review of 4 books on historical trials for TLS, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - "A Stepson of the Republic," review of My France: Politics, Culture, Myth, NYT, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - "Bewitched, Bothered and Bewildered," review of A History of Private Life for The Washington Post, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - "The Judgements of Paris," review of 6 books on French intellectuals, TLS, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - "Chronicles of a Death Foretold," The End of History, circa 1991 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - "To Live in Truth," review of 3 books on Václav Havel for TLS, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - "Ex Oriente Lux? Post-Celebratory Speculations on the 'Lessons' of '89," Towards Greater Europe?, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - "Misjudment of Paris," TLS, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Großbritannien ist anders..." Der Standard, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - "Here Be Monsters," review of Une Utopie Combattante, TLS, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - "The Frontiers of Identity," published for film festival on Jewish life in Eastern Europe, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - "The Past is Another Country," draft, Daedalus draft, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - "The Past is Another Country," draft, Daedalus, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - "Unvollendete Demontage," Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - "Paris and the Tribes of Europe," draft, notes, circa 1992 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - "When the Nazis Sent Home Postcards for Paris," review of The Fall of Paris: June 1940, Newsday, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Review of La France, l'aide américaine et la construction européenne, The Journal of Modern History, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - "Die Vergangenheit ist ein anderes Land," Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - "Betrayal in France," review of The Holocaust, the French and the Jews, NYR, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - "Chauvin and His Heirs," review of 5 books, TLS, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - "Their Favorite Thief," review of 2 books on Jean Genet, NYR, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - "How the East was Won," review of In Europe's Name: Germany and the Divided Continent, NYR, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - "The Inheritors," review of 3 books on European resurgence of extreme right-wing, TLS, 1994 February 11 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - "Entre le tabou et l'obsession," Le Monde, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - "The New Old Nationalism," NYR, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - "The New Old Nationalism," NYR draft, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - "The New Old Nationalism," NYR draft, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - "The New Old Nationalism," NYR notes, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - "The New Old Nationalism," NYR notes, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - "The New Old Nationalism," NYR notes, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - "The New Old Nationalism," NYR notes, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - "The New Old Nationalism," NYR draft, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - "The New Old Nationalism," NYR draft, 2001, undated (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - "Nineteen Eighty-Nine: The End of Which European Era?" Daedalus, copies, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - "Nineteen Eighty-Nine: The End of Which European Era?" Daedalus, German translation, afterward, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - "Truth and Consequence," review of Une jeunesse francaise: François Mitterrand 1934-1947, NYR, drafts, notes, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - "Truth and Consequence," review of Une jeunesse francaise: François Mitterrand 1934-1947, NYR, drafts, notes, research, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - "Truth and Consequence," review of Une jeunesse francaise: François Mitterrand 1934-1947, NYR, drafts, notes, research, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - "How Much is Really Left of the Left?" review of Beyond Right and Left, TLS, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - "The Lost World of Albert Camus," review of Le Premier Homme, NYR, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - "Self-Serving Myths," review of Le Passe D'Une Illusion, TLS, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - "Self-Serving Myths," review of Le Passe D'Une Illusion, TLS, drafts, research, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - "At Home in This Century," review of works by Hannah Arendt and Mary McCarthy, NYR, draft, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - "At Home in This Century," review of works by Hannah Arendt and Mary McCarthy, NYR, drafts, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - "At Home in This Century," review of works by Hannah Arendt and Mary McCarthy, NYR, notes, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - "At Home in This Century," review of works by Hannah Arendt and Mary McCarthy, NYR, notes, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - "At Home in This Century," review of works by Hannah Arendt and Mary McCarthy, NYR, research, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - "At Home in This Century," review of works by Hannah Arendt and Mary McCarthy, NYR, research, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - "At Home in This Century," review of works by Hannah Arendt and Mary McCarthy, NYR, notes, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - "At Home in This Century," review of works by Hannah Arendt and Mary McCarthy, NYR, notes, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - "At Home in This Century," review of works by Hannah Arendt and Mary McCarthy, NYR, letters to the editor, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - "French War Stories," NYT, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - "Low Marx," review of The Wager of Lucien Goldman, TNR, draft, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - "Downhill All the Way," review of The Age of Extremes, Eric Hobsbawm, NYR, drafts, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - "Downhill All the Way," review of The Age of Extremes, Eric Hobsbawm, NYR, notes, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - "Downhill All the Way," review of The Age of Extremes, Eric Hobsbawm, NYR, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - "Temptations of a Superpower," author's response to Judt review, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - "The Ghost of Europes yet to come? Reflections on a presidential speech in France," NYT, notes, drafts, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - "Europe: The Grand Illusion," NYR, drafts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - "Europe: The Grand Illusion," NYR, drafts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - "Europe: The Grand Illusion," NYR, correspondence, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - "Osterreich in Europa," Falter, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - "Holy Warrior", review of His Holiness: John Paul II and the Hidden History of our Time, NYR, notes, drafts, correspondence, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - "Holy Warrior", review of His Holiness: John Paul II and the Hidden History of our Time, NYR, research, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - "Holy Warrior", review of His Holiness: John Paul II and the Hidden History of our Time, NYR, notes, drafts, correspondence, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - "Holy Warrior", review of His Holiness: John Paul II and the Hidden History of our Time, NYR, notes, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - "Holy Warrior", review of His Holiness: John Paul II and the Hidden History of our Time, NYR, notes, drafts, correspondence, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - "Holy Warrior", review of His Holiness: John Paul II and the Hidden History of our Time, NYR, notes, drafts, correspondence, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - "The First Casualties of Capitalism," review of One Hundred Years of Socialism, TLS, drafts, notes, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - "Austria and the Ghost of the New Europe," NYR, drafts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - "Austria and the Ghost of the New Europe," NYR, responses, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - "Austria and the Ghost of the New Europe," NYR, research and notes, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - "Austria and the Ghost of the New Europe," NYR, research and notes, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - "France Without Glory," review of 9 books on 1930s, 1940s France, NYR, responses, notes, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - "France Without Glory," review of 9 books on 1930s, 1940s France, NYR, notes, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - "France Without Glory," review of 9 books on 1930s, 1940s France, NYR, drafts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - "France Without Glory," review of 9 books on 1930s, 1940s France, NYR, drafts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - "France Without Glory," review of 9 books on 1930s, 1940s France, NYR, drafts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - "France Without Glory," review of 9 books on 1930s, 1940s France, NYR, drafts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - "France Without Glory," review of 9 books on 1930s, 1940s France, NYR, drafts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - "Interpreting Genocide," review of Hitler's Willing Executioners, Dimensions research, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - "Interpreting Genocide," review of Hitler's Willing Executioners, Dimensions research, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - "Interpreting Genocide," review of Hitler's Willing Executioners, Dimensions draft, notes, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - "Interpreting Genocide," review of Hitler's Willing Executioners, Dimensions research, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - "Interpreting Genocide," review of Hitler's Willing Executioners, Dimensions research, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - "Interpreting Genocide," review of Hitler's Willing Executioners, Dimensions research, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Review of Whittaker Chambers, TNR, notes, research, drafts, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Review of Whittaker Chambers, TNR, draft, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Review of Whittaker Chambers, TNR, notes, research, drafts, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Review of Whittaker Chambers, TNR, research, drafts, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Review of Whittaker Chambers, TNR, draft, notes, correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, notes, research, drafts, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, drafts, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, notes, research, drafts, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, drafts, correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, notes, research, drafts, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, notes, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, draft, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, reviews by other historians, correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, reviews by other historians, correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, reviews by other historians, correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, reviews by other historians, correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - "Crimes and Misdemeanors," review of Norman Davies' Europe: A History, TNR, reviews by other historians, correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - "Communism Was Mass Murder from the Outset," International Herald Tribune, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Reply to letter to the editor, TNR, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - "The Euro Won't Buy a Genuinely United Europe," International Herald Tribune, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - "Continental Rift," NYT, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - "New Germany, Old NATO," review of 5 books, NYR, responses, research, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - "New Germany, Old NATO," review of 5 books, NYR, responses, research, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - "New Germany, Old NATO," review of 5 books, NYR, draft, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - "New Germany, Old NATO," review of 5 books, NYR, notes, research, drafts, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - "New Germany, Old NATO," review of 5 books, NYR, draft, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - "New Germany, Old NATO," review of 5 books, NYR, draft, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - "The Social Question 'Redivivus,'" Foreign Affairs, correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - "The Social Question 'Redivivus,'" Foreign Affairs, draft, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - "The Social Question 'Redivivus,'" Foreign Affairs, drafts, notes, correspondence, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - "The Social Question 'Redivivus,'" Foreign Affairs, notes, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - "The Social Question 'Redivivus,'" Foreign Affairs, drafts, research, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - "The Social Question 'Redivivus,'" Foreign Affairs, draft, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - "The Social Question 'Redivivus,'" Foreign Affairs, draft, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - "The Social Question 'Redivivus,'" Foreign Affairs, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - "The Longest Road to Hell," review of The Black Book of Communism, NYT, notes, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - "On the Brink," review of 3 books on Cuban Missile Crisis, NYR, drafts, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - "On the Brink," review of 3 books on Cuban Missile Crisis, NYR, draft, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - "On the Brink," review of 3 books on Cuban Missile Crisis, NYR, notes, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - "On the Brink," review of 3 books on Cuban Missile Crisis, NYR, notes, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - "The Stranger," review of Olivier Todd Camus biography, TNR, notes, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - "The Stranger," review of Olivier Todd Camus biography, TNR, notes, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - "The Stranger," review of Olivier Todd Camus biography, TNR, notes, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - "The Stranger," review of Olivier Todd Camus biography, TNR, notes, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - "The Stranger," review of Olivier Todd Camus biography, TNR, notes, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - "The Stranger," review of Olivier Todd Camus biography, TNR, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - "The Reliving of Death," review of Literature of Life, TLS, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - untitled Time article, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - "Counsels on Foreign Relations," review of A Tangled Web: The Making of Foreign Policy in the Nixon Presidency, NYR, draft, correspondence, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - "Counsels on Foreign Relations," review of A Tangled Web: The Making of Foreign Policy in the Nixon Presidency, NYR, draft, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - "Counsels on Foreign Relations," review of A Tangled Web: The Making of Foreign Policy in the Nixon Presidency, NYR, draft, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - "Counsels on Foreign Relations," review of A Tangled Web: The Making of Foreign Policy in the Nixon Presidency, NYR, draft, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - "Counsels on Foreign Relations," review of A Tangled Web: The Making of Foreign Policy in the Nixon Presidency, NYR, notes, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - NYR exchange with Henry Kissinger re: "Counsels on Foreign Relations" piece, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - NYR exchange with Henry Kissinger re: "Counsels on Foreign Relations" piece, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - "Freedom and Freedonia," TNR, notes, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - "Freedom and Freedonia," review of 2 works on Eastern Europe, TNR, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - "The 'Third Way' Is No Route to Paradise," NYT, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - "A la Recherche du Temps Perdu," review of Realms of Memory, NYR, notes, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - "A la Recherche du Temps Perdu," review of Realms of Memory, NYR, notes, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - "A la Recherche du Temps Perdu," review of Realms of Memory, NYR, drafts, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - "A la Recherche du Temps Perdu," review of Realms of Memory, NYR, research, notes, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - "A la Recherche du Temps Perdu," review of Realms of Memory, NYR, draft, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - "A la Recherche du Temps Perdu," review of Realms of Memory, NYR, draft, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - "A la Recherche du Temps Perdu," review of Realms of Memory, NYR, letter to the editor, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - "The Third Way to What? We Need Some Direction," International Herald Tribune, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - "Europe, Still in Search of a Definition," Time special issue, "Visions of Europe", 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - "The Courage of the Elementary," review of Primo Levi: Tragedy of an Optimist, NYR, correspondence, notes, research, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - "The Courage of the Elementary," review of Primo Levi: Tragedy of an Optimist, NYR, research, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - "The Courage of the Elementary," review of Primo Levi: Tragedy of an Optimist, NYR, notes, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - "The Courage of the Elementary," review of Primo Levi: Tragedy of an Optimist, NYR, notes, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - "The Courage of the Elementary," review of Primo Levi: Tragedy of an Optimist, NYR, notes, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - "The Courage of the Elementary," review of Primo Levi: Tragedy of an Optimist, NYR, author, Judt reply, drafts, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - "The Courage of the Elementary," review of Primo Levi: Tragedy of an Optimist, NYR, drafts, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - "Democracies are Weak When Confronting Dictators," International Herald Tribune, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - "Democracy as an Aberration," NYT Book Review, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - "Europe, Without American to Lean On," NYT, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - "Tyrannized by Weaklings," NYT, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - "A New World Disorder," L.A. Times, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - "Is There a Belgium?", NYR, notes, research, responses, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - "Is There a Belgium?", NYR, notes, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - "Is There a Belgium?", NYR, notes, research, responses, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - "Is There a Belgium?", NYR, draft, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - "Is There a Belgium?", NYR, draft, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - "Is There a Belgium?", NYR, draft, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - "Is There a Belgium?", NYR, research, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - "Is There a Belgium?", NYR, research, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - "Is There a Belgium?", NYR, research, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - "Is There a Belgium?", NYR, notes, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - "Is There a Belgium?", NYR, research, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - "Is There a Belgium?", NYR, research, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - "The Morbid Truth," review of The Holocaust in American Life, TNR, drafts, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - "The Morbid Truth," review of The Holocaust in American Life, TNR, notes, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - "On Kosovo: The Reason Why," NYR, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Articles on Kosovo for L.A. Times, NYT, NYR, notes, drafts, research, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Articles on Kosovo for L.A. Times, NYT, NYR, notes, research, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - "A Superpower Flaunts its Arrogance," NYT, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - "The Believer," review of Arthur Koestler: The Homeless Mind, TNR, draft, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - "The Believer," review of Arthur Koestler: The Homeless Mind, TNR, draft, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - "The Believer," review of Arthur Koestler: The Homeless Mind, TNR, notes, research, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - "The Believer," review of Arthur Koestler: The Homeless Mind, TNR, notes, research, draft, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - "The Believer," review of Arthur Koestler: The Homeless Mind, TNR, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - "Extremism Without the Virtue," NYT, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - "Taube Ohren und leere Rhetorik," Die Zeit, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - "Writing History, Facts Optional," op-ed on David Irving for NYT, research, 2000, undated (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - "Tale from the Vienna Woods," NYR piece on Jörg Haider, drafts, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - "Tale from the Vienna Woods,' NYR piece on Jörg Haider, research, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - "Tale from the Vienna Woods,' NYR piece on Jörg Haider, notes, research, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - "Tale from the Vienna Woods,' NYR piece on Jörg Haider, research, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - "The Story of Everything," review of 2 books on world history, NYR, draft, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - "The Story of Everything," review of 2 books on world history, NYR, draft, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - "The Story of Everything," review of 2 books on world history, NYR, notes, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - "The Story of Everything," review of 2 books on world history, NYR, notes, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - "The Story of Everything," review of 2 books on world history, NYR, research, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 85)